(Leonard:)Don't tell Koothrappali.
(Leonard:)-After you.
PENNY: Oh. What a gentleman.
(Penny:)Hey, Sheldon.
[YELLS]
LEONARD:
Oh, my God, are you--? Whoa!
(Sheldon:)Good Lord! You're ruining everything!
(Penny:)-Oh, damn.
-Are you okay?
(Penny:)Do I look okay?
(Leonard:)Don't bark at me. I fell too.
(Penny:)You've been falling all night.
You're used to it.
Sheldon, what are you doing?
(Sheldon:)The same thing I've been doing.
(Sheldon:)Trying to figure out why electrons
have no mass...
-...when traveling through graphene.
-With marbles?
(Sheldon:)I needed something bigger
than peas, now, didn't I?
(Bernadette:)Sheldon, when was the last time
you got any sleep?
(Sheldon:)Two, three days.
(Sheldon:)Not important. I don't need sleep.
I need answers.
(Sheldon:)I need to determine where
in this swamp of unbalanced formulas...
...squateth the toad of truth.
The toad of truth?
Is that a physics thing?
(Leonard:)No. That's a crazy thing.